Thanks for your hard work
Today...
I'm here for a recording of the "A" league.
I wonder how many times I've been on the show since last year's m-league.
I've been on the show every month this year, so I've been on the show more than 10 times.
I learned a lot of things from the league last year and I started to watch the m-League after I appeared in the league.
I've learned a lot about the rules of mahjong, but I've also learned a lot about the depth and fun of the m-League.
When I passed by the Telemachine on my way into the studio today, I saw that they had an online event starting this morning, and they told me they'd be there from 6:00 in the morning.
I'm glad to hear that you're going to be there from 6 a.m. today, and I'm so glad that you're going to be there.
I think it's because of all of you who came to the event that we've been able to read so many of your articles every month.
I'm not nervous when I take pictures with everyone.
I've been watching the m-League for a while now, and there's a section for you, Mr. Ogi.
I've been invited to Janso this year for the first time as a member of the m-League.
I did the corner twice, and the location itself was quite free, and they told me that they hoped I would enjoy it.
The recording itself is always warm and I enjoy it very much.
I also look forward to the m-league every week.
I look forward to watching m-league and m-league every week before going to the show, and I've heard from the performers that they have a certain way of thinking about the game.
I also enjoy the various sections of the m-League.
There are also various sections in each show, such as a discussion with the wives of m-leaguers, and even if you don't know much about the m-league or mahjong, there is a lot of interesting stuff on the show.
I'll be on the show from time to time, so please watch it.
After that, I'm thinking of going to Akari Suda's greeting speech at the school arts and crafts.
I'm going to take some pictures of you there, too.
Akarin-san, you've always been so kind to me.
Okay, let's go. I'm off.
So I've come to give you the album.
I'd like to say hello backstage.
Excuse me.
Good morning.
Nice to meet you.
We've just released a new album.
I hope you enjoy it.
I got it.
It's so cute!
Please listen to my first album!
It's my first album!
It's your first album!
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
Who do you like?
But the song "Last Chance Last Dance" is the lead song.
I recommend it.
Okay. - Okay.
I'd love to hear it.
Thank you.
You're always so kind, Ms. Akarin.
She always takes good care of me.
This way is...
This is her.
She's so cute!
She looks like a fish today.
I'm a mess.
I'm a little tense.
You're twinny and spunky.
What's with the flying?
So cute!
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you.
I'll tell you about it as I go through the script.
First of all, there's the usual 32 seconds.
The camera warps down to the studio.
Then there are two shots of Tanaka-san and Akarin.
And then Minamioka-san will ask you about you and Suwari-chan.
How are you playing mahjong these days?
Yes, I am.
Last time we talked about family mahjong, we probably talked about my brother.
My father's sister and her husband can play Mahjong.
My father's sister can play Mahjong.
My sister's husband, my father, my brother and I play Mahjong together.
With my sister's sister.
With my sister's husband.
My sister's husband and
Your father's brother-in-law.
Talk to me about that for a minute.
Uncle... my uncle...
If you say so.
Excuse me.
Tell me about him.
I'm not very good at explaining.
I thought you were supposed to say "uncle.
It makes no difference.
I don't know what I'd say.
I don't know.
Freeing told me about your family again.
He said he's going to start looking at the games during the month.
I think it's Monday.
Monday, before the last game?
About 3 games into the game, Mr. Nakabayashi went up once.
About the same time as Nika's.
In terms of point difference, it's not difficult.
It's not difficult to come in second place.
But I thought it was really cool that he was in 3rd place and not running away.
I always talk about it, but I can't defend.
I play mahjong, and I think that's cool.
I also enjoyed Abe Maz's nice game.
Mr. Suzuki did a great job.
And Mr. Suzuki worked really hard, trying not to finish in last place somehow.
There's the feeling of winning, but I'm also trying not to lose.
but also the feeling of trying not to lose.
It's like they don't want to be the only one to lose.
They're fighting as a team.
I could see that they are fighting as a team.
I'm going to talk about it later in the month.
I'll tell you about it.
Yes, I'm done.
That's all.
Thank you very much.
In the last auction, Mr. Nakabayashi was going for second place, but I thought it would be more Emiril-like if we fought as a team.
Come on.
Thank you very much.
See you later.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Bye-bye.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you very much.
How was today's recording?
Yes, it was.
It was a lot of fun.
It's kind of a live broadcast of the proceedings.
I have a hard time putting together all the comments.
I get a little nervous when I have to say 3, 2, 1.
I think that's the fun of this program.
I think it's one of the joys of the show.
But by appearing on the live broadcast every month, I'm able to grow a lot.
I'm very grateful for the opportunity to be a part of this program.
I'm very grateful for that.
But it's going on air soon, isn't it?
Yes, in about another hour or two.
I won't be able to deliver it in time.
I see.
But it's on every Sunday.
You can even see the rain.
Please take a look.
Thank you so much for coming out to see us.
We're doing our best to get the word out.
I'm not sure if it's coming through the glass.
I don't know if you can understand what I'm saying.
Thank you for staying late.
Please come back anytime.
Thank you very much.